(Howard:)That's kind of an overreaction
to a little harmless necrophilia.
(Leonard:)It's not you, Howard.
He says he's moving out.
(Raj:)What did you do?
(Raj:)Did you change the contrast
or brightness settings on the television?
(Leonard:)- No.
- Did you take a Band-Aid off...
(Raj:)...in front of him?
(Leonard:)- No.
- Did you buy generic ketchup?
Forget to rinse the sink?
Talk to him through the bathroom door?
Adjust the thermostat? Cook with cilantro?
Pronounce the T in "often"?
(Leonard:)No.
(Howard:)Did you make fun of trains?
(Leonard:)I didn't do anything.
He's just gone insane.
(Raj:)Well, we all knew this day was coming.
(Leonard:)That was fast.
(Sheldon:)It's my pre-packed
disaster evacuation bag.
It's recommended by
the Department of Homeland Security.
(Sheldon:)And Sarah Connor.